Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory7 Mss.B.B61.inventory07
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents K
  - Kroeber, A.L. (Box 53)
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 26
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 4
    - To Boas, 1913 Sept. 4
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 31; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1914 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 10
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 12
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 22; telegram
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 24
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 5
    - To Boas, 1914 Mar. 6; telegram
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 7
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 May 31
    - To Boas, 1916 July 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Sept. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Sept. 17
    - To Boas, 1916 Nov. 21
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 5
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 7
    - To Boas, 1916 Dec. 18
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 16
    - To Boas, 1917 Jan. 25
    - To Boas, 1917 Feb. 8
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 24
    - To Boas, 1917 May 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Sept. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Sept. 21
    - To Boas, 1917 Nov. 10
    - To Boas, 1918 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Sept. 16; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Dec. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Jan. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Jan. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Jan. 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Feb. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Feb. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Sept. 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 21; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 25; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Sept. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1922 Dec. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Sept. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 May 4; 2p.
    - (Enc: Kroeber, A.L. Statement of linguistic research in Calif. May 4, 1927.), 1927 May 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 May 4
    - (Enc. originally with Kroeber, A.L. May 4, 1927), 1927 May 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 June 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 July 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 July 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 July 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Nov. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 4; 1p.
      (Attached 2 receipts for typing by G.G. Chanquet.)
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Feb. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 May 8; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 May 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 May 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 May 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 28; telegram
    - To Boas, 1930 June 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 June 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 June 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 June 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 July 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 22; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 24; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 26; telegram
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 5; telegram
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 9; telegram
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 4; teleg.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 17; teleg.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 21; teleg.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 22; teleg.
    - To Boas, 1931 June 3; 2p.
    - See Boas, F. to Woodworth, R.S. Sept. 2, 1931., 1932 July 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 May 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 June 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Aug. 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Feb. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 15; teleg.
    - To Boas, 1937 May 19; 1p.
    - (Enc: List, 3p.), 1937 Oct. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 14; 1p.
    - (Enc: Steinen, Diether v.d. to Kroeber Nov. 12, 1937), 1938 July 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 27; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 May 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 June 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 May 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 June 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Aug. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Jan. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Feb. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Aug. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 July 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Oct. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - A.L. Kroeber -- to L. Bloomfield, 1940 Jan. 19; 1p.
    - A.L. Kroeber -- to L. Bloomfield, 1940 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - A.L. Kroeber -- to E.P. Boas, 1943 Feb. 19; 2p.
    - A.L. Kroeber -- from E.P. Boas, 1943 Feb. 24
    - A.L. Kroeber -- to B.C. Edel, 1942 Jan. 5; 2p.
    - A.L. Kroeber -- from B.C. Edel
      - (See Edel to Cowan, J.M., Dec. 30, 1942)
      - (See Edel to Bloomfield, L., Jan. 6, 1943)
    - A.L. Kroeber -- to B.C. Edel, 1943 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - A.L. Kroeber -- to James O. Griffin, 1905 Oct. 31; 1p.
      - (See Kroeber, A.L., Nov. 1, 1905)
    - A.L. Kroeber -- to F.W. Hodge, 1902 Aug. 16; 2p.
    - A.L. Kroeber -- to F.W. Hodge, 1907 Oct. 29
    - A.L. Kroeber -- from J.C. Merriam, 1907 Mar. 3
    - A.L. Kroeber -- to E. Sapir, 1913 Mar. 18; 5p.
    - A.L. Kroeber -- to H.K. Schilling, 1905 Oct. 31; 1p.
      - (See Kroeber, A.L., Nov. 1, 1905)
    - A.L. Kroeber -- from D. v.d. Steinen, 1937 Nov. 12
      - (Found in enc. Kroeber, A.L., Jan. 14, 1938)
    - A.L. Kroeber -- to D. v.d. Stienen, 1938 May 23; 1p.
    - A.L. Kroeber -- to M. Swadesh, 1940 Jan. 19; 1p.
    - A.L. Kroeber -- to M. Swadesh, 1940 Jan. 25; 1p.
    - A.L. Kroeber -- to A.M. Tozzer, 1908 Jan. 6
    - A.L. Kroeber -- to A.M. Tozzer, 1917 Jan. 16; 2p.
    - A.L. Kroeber -- to B.I. Wheeler, 1905 Oct. 31; 1p.
      - (See Kroeber, A.L., Nov. 1, 1905)
  - Kroeber, E. (Box 53)
    - To Boas, 1919 Jan. 26; 3p.
  - Kroeber, Johanna (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 10
  - Krogman, Wilton Marion (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1886 Jan. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Nov. 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Nov. 20; 1p.
  - Kronenberg, M. von (Box 53)
    - M. von Kronenberg -- to N.M. Butler, 1935 July 9; 2p.
  - Kroner, R. (Box 53)
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 1; 2p.
  - Krout, J.A. (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1939 May 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 29; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1940 May 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Jan. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Dec. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Jan. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 June 6; 1p.
    - J.A. Krout -- from J.J. Augustin, 1941 Sept. 22
  - Krueger, F. (Box 53)
    - To Boas, 1919 July 12; 2p.
  - Krug, Florian (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 31; 1p.
  - Krumbhaar, E.B. (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1941 Feb. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Feb. 25; 1p.
  - Kruor, B. (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept. 16; 14p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p.
  - Kruss, Hugo (Box 53)
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 May 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 July 6; 1p.
  - Kubisch, H. (Box 53)
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 21; 2p.
  - Kudlich, Herman C. (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1905 May 8; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. to Adams, E.D. Nov. 1, 1905., 1905 Nov. 17; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1906 Apr. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 10
    - (See letter dated Nov. 10, 1908 to Butler, Nicholas Murray), 1918 Nov. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 July 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 May 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 7; postcard
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb.; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 June 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Oct. 29; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 July 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Sept. 5; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 17; 2p.
    - H.C. Kudlich -- to H. Meyer, 1918 June 13; 1p.
  - Kuhl, H.C. (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 13; 1p.
  - Kuhn, E.F. (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 8; 1p.
  - Kuhn, Helmut (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1936 Aug. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 May 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 June 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug 5; 2p
  - Kühn, Herbert (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 June 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Sept. 19; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 May 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 16; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 28; 2p.
  - Kühnemann, A. (Box 53)
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 12; 1p.
  - Kuhnert, Ernst (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1928 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 July 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Aug. 25; 1p.
  - Kuhscher, E. (Box 53)
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 21; 1p.
  - Kuipers, W.E. (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 May 28; 2p.
  - Kulp, D.H. (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 8; 1p.
  - Kulturgeschichtliche Bibliothek, Coln (Box 53)
    See Foy, W.
  - Kunike, H. (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 18; 1p.
  - Kunitz, J. (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 21; 1p.
  - Kunst, D.J. (Box 53)
    - To Boas, 1916 July 29; 2p.
  - Kunst, J. (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1917 June 8
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 19
    - To Boas, 1917 June 6
  - Kunz, George F. (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 9
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 4
    - From Boas, 1913 Mar. 3
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 13
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 31
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 12
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 4
  - Kurath, Hans (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1941 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Apr. 8; 1p.
  - Kürcs, L. (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 15; 1p.
  - Kurtz, F. (Box 53)
    - To Boas, 1885 Jan. 11
  - Kusiw, W. (Box 53)
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 30; 1p.
  - Kuttler, Y. (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Sept. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 9; 1p.
  - Kyriakidis, S. (Box 53)
    - From Boas, 1924 June 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 May 7; 2p.
  - L.,B. (Box 54)
    - B.L. -- to N.M. Butler, 1916 May 11; 2p.
  - L., W. (Box 54)
    - W.L. -- from Rivet?, P., 1920 end